

# Hao Ren (Henry) Yan

2nd Year Student in The University of Sydney

#### Contact

**1** +61 449 017 891

henryhaoyan@gmail.com

#### **Profile**

Hi there! My name is Henry Yan, I am sophomore year student studying Computing and Medical science at The University Of Sydney. Apart from my technical expertise, I am interested in sports such as road cycling, basketball running and swimming (see my Strava account!)

#### **Skills**

Communication

----

C, Python, Java

Organisation

----

Team Work

## Customer Service

their visits.

**Work Experience** 

Singapore Armed Forces · (Full-time)

Apr 2021 - Apr 2023 · (2 yrs 1 mo)

**Transport Operator** 

Amber Seafood · (Part-time)

January 2018 - September 2020

Take ownership of daily operations, prioritise tasks, and ensuring smooth and efficient workflow

• Led teams of VIP drivers ensuring a swift and safe trip for overseas military delegation

• Cultivated a strong safety culture, achieving zero accidents during tenure.

· Served as a national ambassador to foreign military leaders, promoting local culture during

- Maintain high standards of food quality, cleanliness, and customer service; Manage inventory, ordering, and cost control
- Identifying and implement fresh ideas and innovative approaches to enhance the customer experience and drive business growth.

## Languages

English

Mandarin

Cantonese

---

## **Side Hustles**

## **Project Name**

- Primary school Tutoring
- Bible Study Leader
- USYD Volunteering Team

#### **Education**

## The University of Sydney

Bachelor of Advanced Computing and Bachelor of Medical Science (2nd Year)

2024 - current

- Interpersonal and team working skills through Mentoring program
- Various Computing skills through Syncs Hack, Bioinfomatics Hackathon and Workshops.

#### **Nanyang Technological University**

Bachelor of Computing in Computer Science (1st Year)

2023 - 2024

- Computational and critical thinking using C and python to solve practical problems
- Wellbeing module equipped to manage mental and physical health for us and surrounding

#### Courses

- Computational Thinking 2023
- Surf Life Saving Fundamental -2024
- Leadership Mentoring 2024

## Achievements

- 2nd Place: Bioinfomatics analysis Hackathon 2024
- 1st Place: COMBINE x SUDATA x SPDSC Hackathon 2024
- Outstanding Solider of June 2022

#### References

Thames Leamsuwan, Project leader from The University of Sydney

**1** +61 449 969 187

thamesleamsuwan@gmail.com

-